I'm Rendon Rick's with TJ free in this
我是Rendon Rick的 TJ是免费的
tutorial series we'll learn how to use
系列教程 我们将学习如何使用
the free program to create 2d art
创建2D艺术的免费程序
and photo edit our images if you're not
如果你不是 还可以编辑我们的照片
familiar with it's a free program
熟悉它是一个免费的程序
available for Windows Linux and Mac and
适用于Windows、Linux和Mac 并且
it's very similar to Adobe Photoshop
它与Adobe Photoshop非常相似
this is a free open-source program
这是一个免费的开源程序
that's free forever and very
这是永远免费的 而且非常
full-featured and professional in this
功能齐全且专业
tutorial series we'll learn how to use
系列教程 我们将学习如何使用
from a very basic level I'll teach
从最基本的层面来说 我会教你
you how to install it and then we'll
你如何安装它 然后我们将
learn the basic tools how to create a
了解基本工具如何创建
new project how to manage that project
新项目如何管理该项目
and export our images in different file
并将我们的图像导出到不同的文件中
formats I use just about every day
我几乎每天都在使用的格式
to resize images and to do quick little
调整图像大小并快速完成小操作
edits but I do want to say that there
编辑 但我确实想在这里说
are some different alternatives
是否有一些不同的替代方案
depending on what you want to do if
取决于您想要做什么 如果
you're interested in digital art you
你对数字艺术感兴趣 你
should really look into credo
真的应该研究一下信条
it's also an open source project that is
它也是一个开放源码项目
much more geared towards working with
更多地面向与
brushes and kind of recreating the the
画笔和一种重现
aesthetics of fine art and creating art
美术美学与创作艺术
on a computer I would steer away from
在我会避开的电脑上
using for that purpose even though
即使为了这个目的而使用
you can use for creating digital
你可以用来创建数字
art also if you're working with raw
如果您使用RAW 也可以使用ART
photos or you're working with just
照片或您正在使用的只是
photography where you're just trying to
摄影 你只是想要
adjust the colors there's a really good
调整一下颜色 真的很好
free program called darktable for that
为此而调用的免费程序Darktable
it's similar to Adobe Lightroom and it's
它类似于Adobe Lightroom 它是
going to be a very much more powerful
将会是一个非常强大的
tool than for working with actual
工具 而不是使用实际的
photos including raw photos but if all
照片包括原始照片 但如果都是
you want to do is some basic edits you
您想要做的是对您进行一些基本编辑
want to maybe touch-up photos
我想要一些修饰过的照片
is a great tool for that I've used
是我用过的一个很棒的工具
it in the past for repairing tears on
它在过去用来修补撕裂的东西
photographs and and maybe taking out
照片 也许还会带出去
parts of photos where you race a part of
你参加比赛的照片的一部分
it or you take two different pictures
它或者你拍了两张不同的照片
and composite them on top of each other
并将它们叠加在一起
so a lot of great powerful things if you
所以很多强大的东西如果你
work a lot in web or you want to like
经常在网上工作 或者你想要喜欢
quickly design like an ad bar or
快速设计像广告栏
something imp is a great tool for that
一些小东西是一个伟大的工具
just an all-around good tool to have so
只是一个全面的好工具
I'm glad you found this tutorial series
很高兴你找到了这个教程系列
go ahead and check out the other videos
去看看其他视频
I'll include them in the link in the
我会把它们包括在
links for them in the description of
在描述中的链接
this video and if you're interested in
如果你有兴趣
open source software in general check
开源软件在一般检查
out my channel I have playlists on all
在我的频道 我有播放列表上
kinds of open-source software for video
各种开源视频软件
and creative and music and all kinds of
创造力 音乐和各种各样的
things so check those out and go ahead
所以检查一下 然后继续
and don't forget to Like comment
别忘了喜欢评论
subscribe and I look forward to catching
订阅 我期待着赶上
you in the next video
你在下一个视频